Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary until
someone proves it real?
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times,
through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you!
Just like I know you'll stand by me!
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend?
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are
Come, come, bazooka!
We have to retreat!
We're doomed to run for your lives!
Is everyone here?
Okay, buddy, check.
Sound off if you think
you're missing yours.
I'm here!
Got mine.
Right here.
Okay.
Captain Buggy didn't make it back!
He's not all here!
At last, my flashy raft is finished!
I swear, I'll get you! Nooo!
That luck just makes me stronger!
Bring it on!
Lunchtime!
Got you, marpoon!
Just accept it.
Your time has come.
It was just a joke!
Give me!
Closer! Closer!
My plan is perfection!
On! On! On!
On!
On! On! On! Stupid boy! Ha-ha-ha!
Hehehehe! Hehehehe! Hehehehe!
Hehehehe!
I got you!
Oh crap, you got me!
What the hell just happened?!
AAAAAAAA!
Oh! Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Oh no! No!
The end is there! Huh?
Yes!
Where am I?
You must leave!
Says who?
If you want to live, you must leave!
What are these things?
These are the animals of the forest!
If you touch them, you
will be annihilated!
Wow, these guys are flashy!
It's okay.
I warned you not to take another step!
How dare you shoot at me!
Crap, I missed!
There you are!
What the hell?!
You're mine!
Now get out here!
You have Devil Fruit powers!
So what if I do?
You're just a...
you're just a...
What are you?
Like a jack-in-the-box or something?
Yes, ironically, I am in
a box, and my name is...
No, you idiot!
I'm a person, not a toy!
Also, I will kill you if you go anywhere
near my precious animals, so watch it.
I will not hesitate to put you down.
Oh you wanna fight I admire your
stupidity, even if it gets you killed?
That's no fair using weapons!
What the hell do you call this?
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh.
Say your prayers and say them fast!
Shut up, quick escape!
Too bad for you, but I can't allow anyone
to live who tries to hurt these animals.
The only reason anyone ever comes to this
island is to take these precious animals!
Why would I care about
some stupid animals?
Huh? So...
then you're not a poacher?
So what do you think?
It's some pretty good sake,
if I don't say so myself.
Oh, it's the best!
It's been a while since
I've had a good drink.
Have as much as you'd like.
I can always make more.
I'm sorry about that misunderstanding
earlier. Don't worry.
All that's behind us now.
No need to mention it again.
Cheers!
Thanks for helping me
rebuild my flashy raft.
No problem, my friend.
I like working with my hands.
We'll meet again someday.
I'd like that.
Good-bye, my friend!
Take care of yourself!
Good-bye!
Sensei!
I'm sorry I forgot to warn you about
the monsters, but I know you'll be okay.
No, go the other way!
Oh, that's just great! Swim! Go, Buggy!
Hey!
Get out of there!
He looks hungry!
Huh?
What's that?
Oh she's hot wait for me
I haven't seen a woman
in over 20 years well
that's a pirate's luck for!
If I've ever seen it I was worried about
thanks
I owe you
one I thought it was
a Goner for sure it's really no big deal
buggy the pirate cloud right what's it?
to you!
Just who are you, lady?
I'm looking for a certain young pirate.
I think you know
him.
That's him!
Stupid brat!
Just wait till I get my
hands on you! You're dead!
Is that
the guy you're looking for?
I see.
Now I understand.
So that's why you saved my life.
So then, What do you say?
Hell yes!
We both want to kill the same stupid
kids, so we should work together!
That's great.
Let's drink on it.
Captain Buggy!
Before he died, I hated Captain Buggy.
I always thought he was
cruel and heartless.
But now I see how hard he worked.
He really just wanted what
was best for his crew.
Well, Captain Buggy, we were able to
pillage and plunder to all odds content.
I don't know if it'll be the
same with another Captain.
Let's honor our missing leader.
He deserves a flashy goodbye from us.
Rest in peace, Captain.
Leave it to me, your faithful number two.
Cabaji, the acrobat is
ready to take your place!
I will take the helm and lead the buggy
pirates back on the path to glory!
Stop right there!
Cabaji!
It is I,
Beast Tame Emoji,
the captain's right-hand man who should
take his proper place as our leader.
I've always been the next in line and
nobody is going to take that away from me.
I'll be glad to take you
as my second in command!
All right then looks like we'll have a
fight to see who will be the next captain.
That's just fine by me.
KAMETING!
KAMETING! KAMETING!
KAMETING! KAMETING! KAMETING!
KAMETING!
KAMETING! KAMETING!
KAMETING! KAMETING! KAMETING!
KAMET We'll settle this the
old-fashioned way hand-to-hand combat,
and I wouldn't have it any other way now
I get to tear you apart limb from limb
It's no use just give up
You know you can't take it anymore.
I didn't understand anything you just said
Ritchie!
The greatest captain ever!
Captain Richie, Captain
Richie, he's a driver!
After the loss of Captain Buggy,
Ritchie is the one who will lead us now.
All hail Captain Ritchie!
You are trespassing.
This island belongs to the Bearclaw
tribe and you will be shown no mercy.
Help, Captain!
We shall fight to the death.
We surrender.
Did you find something?
Look, that's my ship, the grand
flashy flagship of the Buggy Pirates!
But who would do this?
Who would use such an old picture?
And what did they bury?
Hey, there's somebody passed out
on the ground over there? Huh?
No!
Moji! Cabaji!
What the hell happened to you two?
C-Captain Buggy!
You're alive!
Never leave us again!
We've gone to a camp forever!
I miss you guys so much!
So, uh, who kicked your asses?
I'd like to say hello.
Uh, I don't remember anything
except getting knocked out.
They were attacked, but I
have no idea who did it.
Looks like your boys have been
introduced to the Bearclaw tribe.
We better hurry up if you
want to save your crew.
The Bearclaws are cannibals.
There's a crab in the pot!
You can't eat us now!
I can't die, Pete, myself!
We'll all be dry and stringy anyway!
Just eat this guy!
He looks tasty!
He's got much more meat
in his bones than I do!
Eat him!
This isn't happening!
Don't worry.
It'll all be over soon.
We're the Bearclaw tribe.
We know how to prepare anyone
to taste quite delicious.
What are we gonna do with these things?
Appetizers?
I'm not so sure those chumps
would be very good to eat.
Give them to the dog.
No way.
I think it might make him throw up.
Chop, chop.
Chop, chop, chop, chop!
It can't be!
Jump, Flashy! Reassemble!
And now, my favorite, showtime,
Super Flushing Buggy Ball!
Oh, Ritchie!
Acrobat Techniques!
Extreme Wrath of the Steam Bash!
It's time for the Beast Tape emoji!
I'm Captain Buggy the Clown Pirate!
You didn't really think you'd
be able to hurt me, did you?
Your tribe has done such a
good job looking after my men.
Let me give you your reward.
Like them, boys!
You're some kid!
Chop-chop! Punch!
Try to eat us now!
Thank you!
You saved us!
My adorable little children,
I've missed you all so very much.
Where have you been, Captain, sir?
Please tell us what
happened to you at sea!
That damn Straw Hat is the
reason for all of this.
I promise that I will make him pay!
Um, Captain Buggy, sir?
Who's the pretty lady?
This is the woman who saved
my life, and her name is...
Hold on.
I don't know her name.
Sorry, what was your name again?
Alright!
The Buggy Pirates are back together!
So, Captain, what orders
do you have for us?
To find and kill Monkey D. Luffy!
Me I cannot understand.
As I face what I must do!
I'll say goodbye and screech your hand.
I've said sail alone.
But always now I'm done.
I'll keep you near.
As I drift away.
I pray you watch me as I disappear?
As I watch the sun rise.
I began to wonder.
What could be the reason?
It's so hot inside, no answer has come.
But I can't get away from what's true.
It's because of you.
Show me how to catch those feelings,
get them to come back to me.
I'll do what I must because
they're everything I want will be.
Pack these arms around my dreams
and pull them back from yesterday.
If I'm holding hands with you,
I'm sure that we can make the way.